AFRICA is a place in AFRICA.
EAST AFRICA is a place in AFRICA.
GERMAN EAST AFRICA is a place in AFRICA.
NEU LANGENBURG is a place in AFRICA.
LAKE TANGANYIKA is a place in AFRICA.
IRINGA is a place in AFRICA.
BISMARCKBURG is a place in AFRICA.
TANGA is a place in AFRICA.
KILOSA is a place in AFRICA.
KIONGA is a place in AFRICA.
MAFIA ISLAND is a place in AFRICA.
KILIMATINDE is a place in AFRICA.
NYANGAO is a place in AFRICA.
HANDENI is a place in AFRICA.
VICTORIA NYANZA is a place in AFRICA.
MWITI VALLEY is a place in AFRICA.
MPWAPWA is a place in AFRICA.
SALAAM is a place in AFRICA.
MOROGORO is a place in AFRICA.
THE RUFIJI RIVER is a place in AFRICA.
RUFIJI RIVER is a place in AFRICA.
KONDOA IRANGI is a place in AFRICA.
JASIN is a place in AFRICA.
BEHO-BEHO is a place in AFRICA.
MOSHI is a place in AFRICA.
NEW MOSHI is a place in AFRICA.
KAHE is a place in AFRICA.
LATEMA NEK is a place in AFRICA.
NARUNGOMBE is a place in AFRICA.
KILIMANJARO is a place in AFRICA.
TAVETA is a place in AFRICA.
TSAVO is a place in AFRICA.
NYAMAKURA is a place in AFRICA.
GERMAN SOUTH-WEST AFRICA is a place in AFRICA.
SOUTH-WEST AFRICA is a place in AFRICA.
WINDHUK is a place in AFRICA.
JAKALSWATER is a place in AFRICA.
OTAVIFONTEIN is a place in AFRICA.
AUS is a place in AFRICA.
SWAKOPMUND is a place in AFRICA.
PORTUGUESE WEST AFRICA is a place in AFRICA.
ANGOLA is a place in AFRICA.
SOUTH AFRICA is a place in AFRICA.
UPINGTON is a place in AFRICA.
PERSIA is a place in PERSIA.
WEST PERSIA is a place in PERSIA.
NORTH-WEST PERSIA is a place in PERSIA.
RESHT is a place in PERSIA.
KASVIN is a place in PERSIA.
KARIND is a place in PERSIA.
WESTERN PERSIA is a place in PERSIA.
QASR-I-SHIRIN is a place in PERSIA.
KANGAVAR is a place in PERSIA.
SHIRIN is a place in PERSIA.
QASR-I-SHIRIN is a place in PERSIA.
NORTH PERSIA is a place in PERSIA.
TABRIZ is a place in PERSIA.
URMIA is a place in PERSIA.
DILMAN is a place in PERSIA.
KIRMANSHAH is a place in PERSIA.
HAMADAN is a place in PERSIA.
ENZELI is a place in PERSIA.
SOUTH PERSIA is a place in PERSIA.
BUSHIRE is a place in PERSIA.
SHIRAZ is a place in PERSIA.
EAST PERSIA is a place in PERSIA.
BIRJAND is a place in PERSIA.
KWASH is a place in PERSIA.
MESHED is a place in PERSIA.
KIRMAN is a place in PERSIA.
TEHERAN is a place in PERSIA.
BAKHTIARI is a place in PERSIA.
MESOPOTAMIA is a place in MESOPOTAMIA.
SHARQAT is a place in MESOPOTAMIA.
MUSHAIDIYA is a place in MESOPOTAMIA.
FALAHIYA is a place in MESOPOTAMIA.
RAMADI is a place in MESOPOTAMIA.
NORTHERN MESOPOTAMIA is a place in MESOPOTAMIA.
ROWANDUZ is a place in MESOPOTAMIA.
QURNA is a place in MESOPOTAMIA.
NASIRIYA is a place in MESOPOTAMIA.
KIRKUK is a place in MESOPOTAMIA.
MOSUL is a place in MESOPOTAMIA.
AMARA is a place in MESOPOTAMIA.
THE WADI is a place in MESOPOTAMIA.
SAIHAN is a place in MESOPOTAMIA.
ANA is a place in MESOPOTAMIA.
ISTABULAT is a place in MESOPOTAMIA.
BASRA is a place in MESOPOTAMIA.
SAHIL is a place in MESOPOTAMIA.
HANNA is a place in MESOPOTAMIA.
KHAN BAGHDADI is a place in MESOPOTAMIA.
CTESIPHON is a place in MESOPOTAMIA.
SHAIBA is a place in MESOPOTAMIA.
BAIT AISSA is a place in MESOPOTAMIA.
SAMARRA is a place in MESOPOTAMIA.
TIKRIT is a place in MESOPOTAMIA.
SERBIA is a place in SERBIA.
SOUTH SERBIA is a place in SERBIA.
GEVGELI is a place in SERBIA.
DOIRAN is a place in SERBIA.
PRILEP is a place in SERBIA.
PRISTINA is a place in SERBIA.
MITROVITZA is a place in SERBIA.
OKHRIDA is a place in SERBIA.
DEBRA is a place in SERBIA.
KRAGUJEVATZ is a place in SERBIA.
NORTH SERBIA is a place in SERBIA.
PRIZREN is a place in SERBIA.
MONASTIR is a place in SERBIA.
NISH is a place in SERBIA.
VRANJE is a place in SERBIA.
ISHTIP is a place in SERBIA.
KOLUBARA is a place in SERBIA.
JADAR is a place in SERBIA.
SEMENDRIA is a place in SERBIA.
KACHANIK is a place in SERBIA.
RUSSIA is a place in RUSSIA.
NORTH RUSSIA is a place in RUSSIA.
KADISH is a place in RUSSIA.
PECHENGA is a place in RUSSIA.
OBOZERSKAYA is a place in RUSSIA.
KEM is a place in RUSSIA.
SOUTH RUSSIA is a place in RUSSIA.
KHARKOV is a place in RUSSIA.
NICOLAIEV is a place in RUSSIA.
POLTAVA is a place in RUSSIA.
EKATERINOSLAV is a place in RUSSIA.
ROSTOV is a place in RUSSIA.
EAST RUSSIA is a place in RUSSIA.
KAZAN is a place in RUSSIA.
STERLITAMAK is a place in RUSSIA.
PERM is a place in RUSSIA.
BIRSK is a place in RUSSIA.
LAKE NAROCH is a place in RUSSIA.
WHITE RUSSIA is a place in RUSSIA.
YPRES is a place in YPRES.
ST. JULIEN is a place in YPRES.
YPRES FRONT is a place in YPRES.
GRAVENSTAFEL RIDGE is a place in YPRES.
MOUNT SORREL is a place in YPRES.
FREZENBERG RIDGE is a place in YPRES.
FREZENBERG is a place in YPRES.
NONNEBOSCHEN is a place in YPRES.
POLYGON WOOD is a place in YPRES.
GHELUVELT is a place in YPRES.
MENIN ROAD RIDGE is a place in YPRES.
MENIN is a place in YPRES.
MENIN ROAD is a place in YPRES.
HILL 60 is a place in YPRES.
PASSCHENDAELE is a place in YPRES.
BROODSEINDE is a place in YPRES.
POELCAPELLE is a place in YPRES.
BELLEWAERDE RIDGE is a place in YPRES.
PILCKEM RIDGE is a place in YPRES.
GALICIA is a place in GALICIA.
STRYJ is a place in GALICIA.
BRODY is a place in GALICIA.
LUTKOW is a place in GALICIA.
THE SAN is a place in GALICIA.
TARNAVKA is a place in GALICIA.
ZALESZCZYKI is a place in GALICIA.
HALICZ is a place in GALICIA.
JAROSLAW is a place in GALICIA.
CHYROW is a place in GALICIA.
LEMBERG is a place in GALICIA.
SOMME is a place in SOMME.
GINCHY is a place in SOMME.
8 MILES SOUTH OF THE SOMME is a place in SOMME.
SOUTH OF THE SOMME is a place in SOMME.
LIHONS is a place in SOMME.
THIEPVAL is a place in SOMME.
THIEPVAL RIDGE is a place in SOMME.
TRANSLOY RIDGES is a place in SOMME.
VILLERS-BRETONNEUX is a place in SOMME.
FLERS-COURCELETTE is a place in SOMME.
COURCELETTE is a place in SOMME.
FLERS is a place in SOMME.
ANCRE HEIGHTS is a place in SOMME.
POZIÈRES is a place in SOMME.
POZIÈRES RIDGE is a place in SOMME.
DELVILLE WOOD is a place in SOMME.
GUILLEMONT is a place in SOMME.
MORVAL is a place in SOMME.
BAZENTIN RIDGE is a place in SOMME.
POLAND is a place in POLAND.
NORTH POLAND is a place in POLAND.
PULTUSK is a place in POLAND.
OSOVETS is a place in POLAND.
BENDZIN is a place in POLAND.
RUSSIAN POLAND is a place in POLAND.
TCHENSTOCHOWA is a place in POLAND.
KALISH is a place in POLAND.
NOVO-GEORGIEVSK is a place in POLAND.
VLODAVA is a place in POLAND.
KRASNIK is a place in POLAND.
MLAWA is a place in POLAND.
BREST-LITOVSK is a place in POLAND.
BREST is a place in POLAND.
IVANGOROD is a place in POLAND.
SYEDLETS is a place in POLAND.
BYELOSTOK is a place in POLAND.
CAMEROONS is a place in CAMEROONS.
NGAUNDERE is a place in CAMEROONS.
OYEM is a place in CAMEROONS.
YAUNDE is a place in CAMEROONS.
BANYO is a place in CAMEROONS.
DUALA is a place in CAMEROONS.
EDEA is a place in CAMEROONS.
YABASI is a place in CAMEROONS.
GARUA is a place in CAMEROONS.
MORA is a place in CAMEROONS.
PALESTINE is a place in PALESTINE.
ES SALT is a place in PALESTINE.
HAIFA, ACRE, AND ES SALT are places in PALESTINE.
ACRE is a place in PALESTINE.
HAIFA is a place in PALESTINE.
BEISAN is a place in PALESTINE.
NAZARETH AND BEISAN are places in PALESTINE.
NAZARETH is a place in PALESTINE.
AMMAN is a place in PALESTINE.
EL MUGHAR is a place in PALESTINE.
JAFFA is a place in PALESTINE.
ARMENIA is a place in ARMENIA.
MAMUKHATUN is a place in ARMENIA.
KEUPRI-KEUI is a place in ARMENIA.
RAYAT is a place in ARMENIA.
MAMAKHATUN is a place in ARMENIA.
MUSH is a place in ARMENIA.
ERZINJAN is a place in ARMENIA.
BALTIC is a place in BALTIC.
DAGÖ ISLAND is a place in BALTIC.
MOON ISLAND is a place in BALTIC.
LIBAU is a place in BALTIC.
BALTIC PROVINCES is a place in BALTIC.
SHAVLI is a place in BALTIC.
JAKOBSTADT is a place in BALTIC.
OSEL ISLAND is a place in BALTIC.
ARABIA is a place in ARABIA.
LAHEJ is a place in ARABIA.
SOUTH ARABIA is a place in ARABIA.
SOUTHERN ARABIA is a place in ARABIA.
HODEIDA is a place in ARABIA.
EASTERN ARABIA is a place in ARABIA.
MUSCAT is a place in ARABIA.
WEJH is a place in ARABIA.
AQABA is a place in ARABIA.
JIDDA is a place in ARABIA.
SYRIA is a place in SYRIA.
TRIPOLI is a place in SYRIA.
BEIRUT is a place in SYRIA.
HOMS is a place in SYRIA.
ALEXANDRETTA is a place in SYRIA.
ALEPPO is a place in SYRIA.
SIDON is a place in SYRIA.
MACEDONIA is a place in MACEDONIA.
FLORINA is a place in MACEDONIA.
VARDAR is a place in MACEDONIA.
GREEK FRONTIER OF MACEDONIA is a place in MACEDONIA.
FORT RUPEL is a place in MACEDONIA.
DOBROPOLJE is a place in MACEDONIA.
LEGEN is a place in MACEDONIA.
KRIVOLAK is a place in MACEDONIA.
RUMANIA is a place in RUMANIA.
CRAIOVA is a place in RUMANIA.
FOCSANI is a place in RUMANIA.
BRAILA is a place in RUMANIA.
ARGES is a place in RUMANIA.
MARASESTI is a place in RUMANIA.
MONTENEGRO is a place in MONTENEGRO.
PODGORITZA is a place in MONTENEGRO.
IPEK is a place in MONTENEGRO.
ANTIVARI is a place in MONTENEGRO.
MOUNT LOVCHEN is a place in MONTENEGRO.
CETINJE is a place in MONTENEGRO.
DARDANELLES is a place in DARDANELLES.
SARI BAIR is a place in DARDANELLES.
KRITHIA is a place in DARDANELLES.
GULLY RAVINE is a place in DARDANELLES.
KUM KALE is a place in DARDANELLES.
GEORGIA is a place in GEORGIA.
POTI is a place in GEORGIA.
ALEXANDROPOL is a place in GEORGIA.
KARS is a place in GEORGIA.
BATUM is a place in GEORGIA.
TIFLIS is a place in GEORGIA.
SIBERIA is a place in SIBERIA.
EASTERN SIBERIA is a place in SIBERIA.
DUKHOVSKAYA is a place in SIBERIA.
KHABAROVSK is a place in SIBERIA.
OMSK is a place in SIBERIA.
IRKUTSK is a place in SIBERIA.
BLAGOVYESCHENSK is a place in SIBERIA.
EGYPT is a place in EGYPT.
WESTERN EGYPT is a place in EGYPT.
WADI MAJID is a place in EGYPT.
AGAGIYA is a place in EGYPT.
SOLLUM is a place in EGYPT.
WEST EGYPT is a place in EGYPT.
DAKHLA OASIS is a place in EGYPT.
SIWA is a place in EGYPT.
SIWA OASIS is a place in EGYPT.
ALBANIA is a place in ALBANIA.
SAN GIOVANNI is a place in ALBANIA.
SAN GIOVANNI DI MEDUA is a place in ALBANIA.
ELBASAN is a place in ALBANIA.
BERAT is a place in ALBANIA.
LYS is a place in LYS.
KEMMEL is a place in LYS.
KEMMEL RIDGE is a place in LYS.
BAILLEUL is a place in LYS.
HAZEBROUCK is a place in LYS.
BETHUNE is a place in LYS.
CAUCASUS is a place in CAUCASUS.
SARIKAMISH is a place in CAUCASUS.
RUSSIAN CAUCASUS is a place in CAUCASUS.
KURDAMIR is a place in CAUCASUS.
EAST CAUCASUS is a place in CAUCASUS.
KARA URGAN is a place in CAUCASUS.
DOBRUDJA is a place in DOBRUDJA.
SILISTRA is a place in DOBRUDJA.
CONSTANZA is a place in DOBRUDJA.
TUTRAKAN is a place in DOBRUDJA.
CERNAVODA is a place in DOBRUDJA.
BUKOVINA is a place in BUKOVINA.
CZERNOWITZ is a place in BUKOVINA.
KIMPOLUNG is a place in BUKOVINA.
SOUTHERN BUKOVINA is a place in BUKOVINA.
RADAUTZ is a place in BUKOVINA.
SINAI is a place in SINAI.
MAGDHABA is a place in SINAI.
RAFAH is a place in SINAI.
RUMANI is a place in SINAI.
EL ARISH is a place in SINAI.
ARRAS is a place in ARRAS.
BETWEEN ARRAS AND ALBERT are places in ARRAS.
AYETTE is a place in ARRAS.
ALBERT is a place in ARRAS.
5 MILES SOUTH OF ARRAS is a place in ARRAS.
MERCATEL is a place in ARRAS.
ARLEUX is a place in ARRAS.
VERDUN is a place in VERDUN.
FORT VAUX is a place in VERDUN.
FORT DOUAUMONT is a place in VERDUN.
DOUAUMONT is a place in VERDUN.
FORT THIAUMONT is a place in VERDUN.
THIAUMONT is a place in VERDUN.
CARPATHIANS is a place in CARPATHIANS.
JABLONICA PASS is a place in CARPATHIANS.
THE PLOSKA HEIGHT is a place in CARPATHIANS.
RHODESIA is a place in RHODESIA.
ABERCORN is a place in RHODESIA.
KASAMA is a place in RHODESIA.
CHAMBEZI RIVER is a place in RHODESIA.
TRANSYLVANIA is a place in TRANSYLVANIA.
BRASOV is a place in TRANSYLVANIA.
ALBA-JULIA is a place in TRANSYLVANIA.
SIBIU is a place in TRANSYLVANIA.
EAST PRUSSIA is a place in EAST PRUSSIA.
MEMEL is a place in EAST PRUSSIA.
MASURIA is a place in EAST PRUSSIA.
GAWAITEN-GUMBINNEN is a place in EAST PRUSSIA.
FINLAND is a place in FINLAND.
SOUTH FINLAND is a place in FINLAND.
FREDERICKSHAMN is a place in FINLAND.
VIBORG is a place in FINLAND.
HELSINGFORS is a place in FINLAND.
TREBIZOND is a place in TREBIZOND.
BLACK SEA is a place in TREBIZOND.
ERZERUM is a place in TREBIZOND.
BAIBURT is a place in TREBIZOND.
BETWEEN ERZERUM AND TREBIZOND are places in TREBIZOND.
ASIA MINOR is a place in TREBIZOND.
TRANS-CASPIA is a place in TRANS-CASPIA.
KAAKHKA is a place in TRANS-CASPIA.
DUSHAK is a place in TRANS-CASPIA.
BAIRAM ALI is a place in TRANS-CASPIA.
FRANCE is a place in FRANCE.
ST. OMER is a place in FRANCE.
THE AVRE is a place in FRANCE.
ADRIATIC is a place in ADRIATIC.
PREMUDA ISLAND is a place in ADRIATIC.
PELAGOSA is a place in ADRIATIC.
PACIFIC is a place in PACIFIC.
YAP ISLAND is a place in PACIFIC.
MOPELIA ISLAND is a place in PACIFIC.
LAKE NYASSA is a place in LAKE NYASSA.
MANUNGA is a place in LAKE NYASSA.
160 MILES SOUTH OF LAKE NYASSA is a place in LAKE NYASSA.
SPHINXHAVEN is a place in LAKE NYASSA.
LENS is a place in LENS.
LIÉVIN is a place in LENS.
THE WESTERN SUBURB OF LENS is a place in LENS.
CITÉ ST. PIERRE is a place in LENS.
NORTH-WEST OF LENS is a place in LENS.
KOLOMEA is a place in KOLOMEA.
BULGARIA is a place in BULGARIA.
DEDE AGATCH is a place in BULGARIA.
YAMBOL is a place in BULGARIA.
NORTH-WEST FRONTIER OF INDIA is a place in NORTH-WEST FRONTIER OF INDIA.
INDIA is a place in NORTH-WEST FRONTIER OF INDIA.
MIRANSHAH is a place in NORTH-WEST FRONTIER OF INDIA.
HAFIZ KOR is a place in NORTH-WEST FRONTIER OF INDIA.
STANISLAU is a place in STANISLAU.
TYSMIENICA is a place in STANISLAU.
NEAR STANISLAU is a place in STANISLAU.
MOLDAVIAN REPUBLIC is a place in MOLDAVIAN REPUBLIC.
BESSARABIA is a place in MOLDAVIAN REPUBLIC.
INDEPENDENT MOLDAVIAN REPUBLIC is a place in MOLDAVIAN REPUBLIC.
NEBI SAMWIL is a place in NEBI SAMWIL.
MIZPEH is a place in NEBI SAMWIL.
THE NEBI SAMWIL RIDGE is a place in NEBI SAMWIL.
ESTONIA is a place in ESTONIA.
DORPAT is a place in ESTONIA.
NARVA is a place in ESTONIA.
DARFUR is a place in DARFUR.
GYUBA is a place in DARFUR.
BERINGIYA is a place in DARFUR.
SUVLA is a place in SUVLA.
SCIMITAR HILL is a place in SUVLA.
MURMAN FRONT is a place in MURMAN FRONT.
UKHTINSKAYA is a place in MURMAN FRONT.
PYAVOZERO LAKE is a place in MURMAN FRONT.
ALSACE is a place in ALSACE.
MULHOUSE is a place in ALSACE.
THE HARTMANNSWEILERKOPF is a place in ALSACE.
BITLIS is a place in BITLIS.
LAKE VAN is a place in BITLIS.
SOUTH-WEST OF LAKE VAN is a place in BITLIS.
VAUX is a place in VAUX.
FORT VAUX is a place in VAUX.
NEAR CHÂTEAU-THIERRY is a place in VAUX.
CHÂTEAU-THIERRY is a place in VAUX.
TRENTINO is a place in TRENTINO.
THE COL DI LANA is a place in TRENTINO.
ROVERETO is a place in TRENTINO.
VA. is a place in VA..
HAMPTON ROADS is a place in VA..
VAN is a place in VAN.
LAKE VAN is a place in VAN.
SOUTH-WEST OF LAKE VAN is a place in VAN.
ARCHANGEL is a place in ARCHANGEL.
ARCHANGEL FRONT is a place in ARCHANGEL.
CHAMOVA is a place in ARCHANGEL.
SCUTARI is a place in SCUTARI.
SHKODRA is a place in SCUTARI.
NORFOLK is a place in NORFOLK.
YARMOUTH is a place in NORFOLK.
ADAMELLO DISTRICT is a place in ADAMELLO DISTRICT.
THE MONTICELLO PASS is a place in ADAMELLO DISTRICT.
IN THE ADAMELLO DISTRICT is a place in ADAMELLO DISTRICT.
WALNEY ISLAND is a place in WALNEY ISLAND.
BARROW-IN-FURNESS is a place in WALNEY ISLAND.
NEWPORT is a place in NEWPORT.
UNITED STATES is a place in NEWPORT.
NEWPORT NEWS is a place in NEWPORT.
UNITED STATES OF AMERICA is a place in NEWPORT.
GERMAN GUINEA is a place in GERMAN GUINEA.
BISMARCK ARCHIPELAGO is a place in GERMAN GUINEA.
BAHREIN ISLANDS is a place in BAHREIN ISLANDS.
PERSIAN GULF is a place in BAHREIN ISLANDS.
ADEN is a place in ADEN.
IMAD is a place in ADEN.
EAST OF MONCHY is a place in EAST OF MONCHY.
MONCHY is a place in EAST OF MONCHY.
INFANTRY HILL is a place in EAST OF MONCHY.
ATLANTIC COAST is a place in ATLANTIC COAST.
FIRE ISLAND is a place in ATLANTIC COAST.
SABOR is a place in SABOR.
CROATION CONGRESS is a place in SABOR.
KILDA is a place in KILDA.
HEBRIDES is a place in KILDA.
CASPIAN SEA is a place in CASPIAN SEA.
BAKU is a place in CASPIAN SEA.
ÆGEAN is a place in ÆGEAN.
CHIOS is a place in ÆGEAN.
KHANAQIN is a place in KHANAQIN.
NORTH-EAST OF BAGHDAD is a place in KHANAQIN.
BAGHDAD is a place in KHANAQIN.
VILNA is a place in VILNA.
EAST OF VILNA is a place in VILNA.
LAKE NAROTCH is a place in VILNA.
CAROLINE ISLANDS is a place in CAROLINE ISLANDS.
PONAPE is a place in CAROLINE ISLANDS.
HEJAZ is a place in HEJAZ.
TAIF is a place in HEJAZ.
HARTLEPOOL is a place in HARTLEPOOL.
EAST COAST OF ENGLAND is a place in HARTLEPOOL.
ENGLAND is a place in HARTLEPOOL.
GRICOURT is a place in GRICOURT.
NEAR ST. QUENTIN is a place in GRICOURT.
ST. QUENTIN is a place in GRICOURT.
NYASSALAND is a place in NYASSALAND.
KARONGA is a place in NYASSALAND.
BAGAMOYO is a place in BAGAMOYO.
GERMAN EAST AFRICAN COAST is a place in BAGAMOYO.
CAPO SILE is a place in CAPO SILE.
NORTH OF THE VENETIAN LAGOONS is a place in CAPO SILE.
THE VENETIAN LAGOONS is a place in CAPO SILE.
LJUBLJANA is a place in LJUBLJANA.
LAIBACH is a place in LJUBLJANA.
ORSOVA is a place in ORSOVA.
HUNGARY is a place in ORSOVA.
KAMINA is a place in KAMINA.
TOGOLAND is a place in KAMINA.
FUNCHAL is a place in FUNCHAL.
MADEIRA is a place in FUNCHAL.
MONTDIDIER is a place in MONTDIDIER.
AMIENS is a place in MONTDIDIER.
COMPIÈGNE is a place in MONTDIDIER.
BETWEEN AMIENS AND COMPIÈGNE are places in MONTDIDIER.
BELGIUM is a place in BELGIUM.
TERMONDE is a place in BELGIUM.
SEMLIN is a place in SEMLIN.
SYRMIA is a place in SEMLIN.
TSINGTAU is a place in TSINGTAU.
KIAO-CHAU is a place in TSINGTAU.
SCARBOROUGH is a place in SCARBOROUGH.
YORKSHIRE is a place in SCARBOROUGH.
VENETIA is a place in VENETIA.
UDINE is a place in VENETIA.
PONTA DELGADA is a place in PONTA DELGADA.
AZORES is a place in PONTA DELGADA.
SHARON AND NABLUS are places in SHARON AND NABLUS.
MEGIDDO is a place in SHARON AND NABLUS.
GREECE is a place in GREECE.
JANINA is a place in GREECE.
CUMBERLAND is a place in CUMBERLAND.
WHITEHAVEN is a place in CUMBERLAND.
TRANS CASPIA is a place in TRANS CASPIA.
MERV is a place in TRANS CASPIA.
BREMEN is a place in BREMEN.
GERMANY is a place in BREMEN.
SUFFOLK is a place in SUFFOLK.
LOWESTOFT is a place in SUFFOLK.
GALLIPOLI is a place in GALLIPOLI.
GALLIPOLI PENINSULA is a place in GALLIPOLI.
HELLES is a place in GALLIPOLI.
SOVDEP is a place in SOVDEP.
MURMAN SOVIET is a place in SOVDEP.
STAVANGER is a place in STAVANGER.
NORWAY is a place in STAVANGER.
MONFALCONE is a place in MONFALCONE.
ISOUZO is a place in MONFALCONE.
CORONEL is a place in CORONEL.
CHILE is a place in CORONEL.
UKRAINE is a place in UKRAINE.
KIEV is a place in UKRAINE.
LIBERIA is a place in LIBERIA.
MONROVIA is a place in LIBERIA.
BLAAVANDS HUK is a place in BLAAVANDS HUK.
DENMARK is a place in BLAAVANDS HUK.
TALASSIA is a place in TALASSIA.
NEU POMMERN is a place in TALASSIA.
KRONSTADT is a place in KRONSTADT.
BRASSO is a place in KRONSTADT.
AISNE is a place in AISNE.
CRAONNE is a place in AISNE.
MORTAGNE is a place in MORTAGNE.
VOSGES is a place in MORTAGNE.